<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Orlando Orientation</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="category_attractions">ATTRACTIONS</string>
    <string name="category_beaches">BEACHES</string>
    <string name="category_restaurants">RESTAURANTS</string>
    <string name="category_nightlife">NIGHTLIFE</string>
    <string name="walt_disney_world">Walt Disney World</string>
    <string name="universal_studios">Universal Studios</string>
    <string name="seaworld">SeaWorld</string>
    <string name="busch_gardens">Busch Gardens</string>
    <string name="legoland">LegoLand</string>
    <string name="hard_rock_cafe">Hard Rock Casino</string>
    <string name="orlando_icon">Orlando Icon</string>
    <string name="kennedy_space_center">Kennedy Space Center</string>
    <string name="cocoa">Cocoa</string>
    <string name="clearwater">Clearwater</string>
    <string name="vero">Vero</string>
    <string name="madeira">Madeira</string>
    <string name="st_pete">St. Pete</string>
    <string name="new_smyrna">New Smyrna</string>
    <string name="port_canaveral">Port Canaveral</string>
    <string name="daytona">Daytona</string>
    <string name="orlando_city_soccer">Orlando City Soccer</string>
    <string name="orlando_magic">Orlando Magic</string>
    <string name="disney_springs">Disney Springs</string>
    <string name="citywalk">CityWalk</string>
    <string name="i_drive">International Drive</string>
    <string name="downtown_orlando">Downtown Orlando</string>
    <string name="oceanaire">Oceanaire</string>
    <string name="yard_house">Yard House</string>
    <string name="maggianos">Maggiano\'s</string>
    <string name="normans">Norman\'s</string>
    <string name="kekes">Keke\'s</string>
    <string name="cowfish">The Cowfish</string>
    <string name="bull_and_bear"><![CDATA[Bull & Bear]]></string>
    <string name="la_luce">La Luce</string>
    <string name="info_walt_disney_world">The Walt Disney World Resort, commonly known as Walt Disney World, or often just as Disney World, is an entertainment complex in Bay Lake and Lake Buena Vista, Florida, near Orlando and Kissimmee, Florida.</string>
    <string name="info_universal_studios"><![CDATA[The Universal Orlando Resort, commonly known as Universal Orlando, formerly Universal Studios Escape, is an American theme park and entertainment resort complex based in Orlando, Florida. The resort is operated by Universal Parks & Resorts.]]></string>
    <string name="info_seaworld"><![CDATA[SeaWorld Orlando is a theme park and marine zoological park, in Orlando, Florida. It is owned and operated by SeaWorld Parks & Entertainment.]]></string>
    <string name="info_busch_gardens">Busch Gardens Tampa is a 335-acre African-themed animal theme park located in the city of Tampa, Florida.</string>
    <string name="info_legoland">LEGOLAND Florida Resort, the largest LEGOLAND park in the world, is a 150-acre interactive theme park geared towards families just 45-minutes from Orlando. The park features more than 50 rides, shows and attractions, restaurants, shopping, and a breathtaking botanical garden.</string>
    <string name="info_hard_rock_casino"><![CDATA[Seminole Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Tampa is the premier entertainment destination of Central Florida and the place where celebrities love to stay and play. This electrifying casino is one of the largest casinos in the world, and features thousands of the hottest slot machines.]]></string>
    <string name="info_orlando_icon"><![CDATA[Sizable destination with an observation wheel, aquarium & wax museum, plus shops & restaurants.]]></string>
    <string name="info_kennedy_space_center">The John F. Kennedy Space Center is one of ten National Aeronautics and Space Administration field centers. Since December 1968, Kennedy Space Center has been NASA\'s primary launch center of human spaceflight.</string>
    <string name="info_cocoa">Cocoa Beach is a Florida city south of Cape Canaveral Air Force Station. The city is known for its beach and surf. Inside the Florida Surf Museum traces the local history. Nearby Cocoa Beach Pier has eateries and shops.</string>
    <string name="info_clearwater">Clearwater Beach includes a resort area and a residential area on the Gulf of Mexico in Pinellas County on the west central coast of Florida.</string>
    <string name="info_vero_beach">Vero Beach is a small Florida city, with Atlantic-facing beaches on a barrier island across the Indian River Lagoon. On the outskirts, McKee Botanical Garden has tropical plants and water lily–filled streams. To the north, Pelican Island National Wildlife Refuge shelters brown pelicans.</string>
    <string name="info_madeira">Madeira Beach is a city in Pinellas County, Florida, United States, bordered on the west by the Gulf of Mexico and on the east by St. Petersburg. As of the 2010 census, the population was 4,263.</string>
    <string name="info_st_pete">St. Pete Beach is a Florida resort city set on a barrier island, west of St. Petersburg. It’s known for its beaches. The Pass-A-Grille area offers galleries, shops and the Gulf Beaches Historical Museum. Nearby, boats depart to Shell Key, a nesting site for seabirds and turtles.</string>
    <string name="info_new_smyrna">New Smyrna Beach is a Florida city south of Daytona Beach. It’s a surf hub known for its beaches, including nearby Canaveral National Seashore. Downtown’s palm-lined Canal Street Historic District has art galleries, shops and the New Smyrna Museum of History.</string>
    <string name="info_port_canaveral">Port Canaveral is a cruise, cargo and naval port in Brevard County, Florida, United States. It is one of the busiest cruise ports in the world with 3.9 million cruise passengers passing through during 2014.</string>
    <string name="info_daytona">Daytona Beach is a city on Florida’s Atlantic coast. It’s known for Daytona International Speedway, which hosts February’s iconic Daytona 500 NASCAR race. The beach has hard-packed sand where driving is permitted in designated areas. Daytona Beach Bandshell stages free summer concerts.</string>
    <string name="info_orlando_city_soccer">Orlando City Soccer Club is an American professional soccer club in Orlando, Florida, that competes as a member of the Eastern Conference in Major League Soccer.</string>
    <string name="info_orlando_magic">The Orlando Magic are an American professional basketball team based in Orlando, Florida. The Magic compete in the National Basketball Association as a member of the league\'s Eastern Conference Southeast Division.</string>
    <string name="info_disney_springs">Disney Springs is an outdoor shopping, dining, and entertainment complex at the Walt Disney World Resort in Bay Lake, Florida, near Orlando.</string>
    <string name="info_citywalk">Universal CityWalk is a 30-acre nighttime entertainment complex offering some of the hottest, most recognizable entertainment experiences in the world with dozens of clubs, restaurants and shops. It’s open until 2 AM, and all guest can self-park for free after 6PM.</string>
    <string name="info_i_drive">The International Drive Resort Area provides visitors to the Orlando area with world-class attractions, entertainment, dining and shopping fun for the entire family that gives guests a reason to visit Orlando\'s Most Dynamic Destination!</string>
    <string name="info_downtown_orlando">Downtown Orlando is the largest urban center in Central Florida. It is home to residential and commercial towers; local, state, and federal government offices; sports facilities; performing arts theaters; art galleries; a movie theater; nightclubs; and host numerous events year round!</string>
    <string name="info_oceanaire"><![CDATA[High-end chain offering seafood, steaks & a deep wine list in sophisticated but lively environs.]]></string>
    <string name="info_yard_house"><![CDATA[High-end sports-bar chain with a huge menu of New American fare & an extensive list of draft beers.]]></string>
    <string name="info_maggianos">Semi-upscale chain for classic Italian fare served family-style in a relaxed, polished space.</string>
    <string name="info_normans">Elegant space in a Ritz-Carlton for Norman Van Aken\'s sophisticated new-world cuisine.</string>
    <string name="info_kekes">Best breakfast in Orlando!</string>
    <string name="info_cowfish"><![CDATA[Bustling, family-friendly fusion eatery at Universal CityWalk with burgers, sushi & a full bar.]]></string>
    <string name="info_bull_and_bear">The Waldorf Astoria\'s high-end steak destination with clubby quarters lit by chandeliers.</string>
    <string name="info_la_luce">Napa-influenced, seasonal Italian fare in a hotel\'s sleek, art-filled restaurant.</string>
    <string name="call_ahead">Call Ahead\n</string>
    <string name="contact_oceanaire">(407)363-4801</string>
    <string name="contact_yard_house">(407)351-8220</string>
    <string name="contact_maggianos">(407)241-8650</string>
    <string name="contact_normans">(407)393-4333</string>
    <string name="contact_kekes">(407)226-1400</string>
    <string name="contact_cowfish">(407)224-3663</string>
    <string name="contact_bull_and_bear">(407)597-5500</string>
    <string name="contact_la_luce">(407)597-3600</string>
</resources>